revisionfx.com 2014-11-21

# RE:Vision Effects, Inc. : Company: Legal Notices

Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement for RE:Vision Effects, Inc.

RE:Vision Effects, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: RE:Vision Effects, Inc..

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

Our Yahoo! store [(http://store.yahoo.com/revisionfx)](http://revisionfx.stores.yahoo.net/products.html/products.html) uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. For Yahoo! store privacy policies, please see their privacy statement at <http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/>.

This site contains links to other sites. RE:Vision Effects, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses a Yahoo! order form to request information from visitors. Yahoo! store collects visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Customer information collected by our Yahoo! store is used by Yahoo! as described in <http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us>.

RE:Vision Effects does not distribute or sell information collected by our Yahoo! store to any other 3rd party. However, Yahoo! itself stores and uses information collected for our store as described in <http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us>.

Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

You can send email to info (at) revisionfx (dot) com

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact

**Webmaster**  
RE:Vision Effects, Inc.  
18 Vicksburg Street  
San Francisco,CA 94114  
info (at) revisionfx (dot) com
